

Steven Matchett

Work History

Realtor.com - Software Engineer - Full Stack Morgantown, WV 10/2016 - Current

- Developer for Realsuite a dashboard for Agents, Offices, and Brokers to manager listings, contacts, leads, branding, and more
- Developed WebdriverIO jenkin integrations using storybook to smoke test react components
- Contributed to the migration to React and to manager listings, contacts, leads, branding, and more
- Led data synchronizing of accounts between ListHub (acquired startup) and Realtor.com

MATRIC Research - Software Engineer Morgantown, WV 05/2013 - 10/2016

- Developer for Energy Data eXchange (EDX) a website created for a secure environment for multi-organizational research teams to share, build, and collaborate on energy data
- Created multi-level security framework for users to share data privately within select groups
- Develop multiple REST APIs for third party systems to utilize large datasets in GIS and hadoop applications

MATRIC Research - Software Engineering Intern Morgantown, WV 01/2013 - 05/2013

WVU Biometric Systems Lab - Research Assistant Morgantown, WV 01/2012 - 12/2012

 Developed software for a military sponsor where I created an AI software package, which integrated multiple hardware devices to monitor a subject's physiological changes during the course of an interrogation me@StevenMatchett.com (973) 945-8572 Morgantown, WV 26508

Professional Summary

Experienced working with teams to produce impactful, leading-edge websites that engage customers and deliver business results. Well-versed in design standards and user preferences.

Skills

React, Python, Pyramids (MVC), Node, Git, SQL, Redis, GraphQL, Java, WebdriverIO, Jenkins, Storybooks, Scrum

Education

West Virginia University (2013) Morgantown, WV Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

• Major G.P.A = 3.7 / 4.0

Contacts

 Mark Dehlin - Director of Software Email: mark.dehlin@matricinnovates.com Phone: (304) 720-8619

 Ph.D. Thirimachos Bourlai - Professor Email:

Thirimachos.Bourlai@mail.wvu.edu Phone: (832) 713-9773